Mana: Beyond Belief documentary film collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 8: Burma
  - Prome, November 19-24, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 3 pages; "Pyay Paya" (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 113, 2002-11-19 to 2002-11-22, AFC 2019/001: MV113; This item is also listed in Series 8, Kyaikto.; afc2019001_0113; 51 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder"), Shwesandaw Pagoda
      - HDCAM Tape 114, 2002-11-22 to 2002-11-23, AFC 2019/001: MV114; afc2019001_0114; 49 min.; Shwesandaw Pagoda, Sehtatgyi Paya (giant Buddha statue)
      - HDCAM Tape 115, 2002-11-23, AFC 2019/001: MV115; afc2019001_0115; 49 min.; Shwesandaw Pagoda, Sehtatgyi Paya (giant Buddha statue)
      - HDCAM Tape 116, 2002-11-23 to 2002-11-24, AFC 2019/001: MV116; This item is also listed in Series 8, Rangoon.; afc2019001_0116; 49 min.; Shwesandaw Pagoda, Sehtatgyi Paya (giant Buddha statue), Irrawaddy River, Hlawga National Park, Shwenyaungbin Bo Bo Gyi shrine ("car shrine")
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 105, 2002-11-22 to 2002-11-23, AFC 2019/001: SR105; afc2019001_DAT0105; 1 hr. 33 min.; Shwesandaw Pagoda
      - DAT Tape 106, 2002-11-23 to 2002-11-24, AFC 2019/001: SR106; afc2019001_DAT0106; 1 hr. 40 min.; Shwesandaw Pagoda, Sehtatgyi Paya (giant Buddha statue), Shwenyaungbin Bo Bo Gyi shrine ("car shrine")
- Series 9: India
  - Bangalore, November 28-30, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Translations and transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 50 pages; Kannada, English (Box-folder 2/27)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 6 pages; "Computer's blessing," "Gods' web site," "Infosys," "kitchen ceremony," "Streets in Bangalore" (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 118, 2002-11-28, AFC 2019/001: MV118; afc2019001_0118; 49 min.; Online Darshan website
      - HDCAM Tape 119, 2002-11-28, AFC 2019/001: MV119; afc2019001_0119; 43 min.; Online Darshan website, Infosys Technologies business campus, city and street views
      - HDCAM Tape 120, 2002-11-29, AFC 2019/001: MV120; afc2019001_0120; 49 min.; Kitchen worship, Infosys Technologies business campus, Infosys Technologies COO Kris Gopalakrishnan
      - HDCAM Tape 121, 2002-11-29 to 2002-11-30, AFC 2019/001: MV121; afc2019001_0121; 48 min.; Infosys Technologies business campus, Infosys Technologies COO Kris Gopalakrishnan
      - HDCAM Tape 122, 2002-11-29 to 2002-11-30, AFC 2019/001: MV122; afc2019001_0122; 48 min.; Infosys Technologies business campus, city and street views, new computer blessing
      - HDCAM Tape 123, 2002-11-30 to 2002-12-11, AFC 2019/001: MV123; This item is also listed in Series 10, Pawarenga.; afc2019001_0123; 49 min.; New computer blessing, Malcolm Peri, Maori marae (meeting house)
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 108, 2002-11-28, AFC 2019/001: SR108; afc2019001_DAT0108; 1 hr. 30 min.; Online Darshan website, Infosys Technologies business campus
      - DAT Tape 109, 2002-11-29, AFC 2019/001: SR109; afc2019001_DAT0109; 1 hr. 32 min.; Kitchen worship, Infosys Technologies business campus, Infosys Technologies COO Kris Gopalakrishnan
      - DAT Tape 110, 2002-11-29 to 2002-11-30, AFC 2019/001: SR110; afc2019001_DAT0110; 1 hr. 8 min.; Infosys Technologies business campus, city and street sounds, new computer blessing
- Series 10: New Zealand
  - Whangarei, December 7-9, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 98 pages; English (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Transcriptions, circa 2003-03-11, 10_NewZealand_Whangarei_Transcriptions; 7 files (.pdf, .doc); English, Maori (Digital-content afc2019001_dc002)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 8 pages; "Itv Wallace HETERAKA chez lui," "Itv Wallace in the forest," "Itv Wallace in/out the Marae," "objects chez Wallace," "Carvings" (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 124, 2002-12-07, AFC 2019/001: MV124; afc2019001_0124; 49 min.; Wallace Hetaraka
      - HDCAM Tape 125, 2002-12-07, AFC 2019/001: MV125; afc2019001_0125; 49 min.; Wallace Hetaraka
      - HDCAM Tape 126, 2002-12-07, AFC 2019/001: MV126; afc2019001_0126; 50 min.; Wallace Hetaraka
      - HDCAM Tape 127, 2002-12-07, AFC 2019/001: MV127; afc2019001_0127; 49 min.; Wallace Hetaraka
      - HDCAM Tape 128, 2002-12-08, AFC 2019/001: MV128; afc2019001_0128; 50 min.; Wallace Hetaraka, Terenga Paraoa (Maori marae [meeting house])
      - HDCAM Tape 129, 2002-12-08 to 2002-12-09, AFC 2019/001: MV129; afc2019001_0129; 45 min.; Wallace Hetaraka, Terenga Paraoa (Maori marae [meeting house]), Waipoua Forest, Tāne Mahuta (kauri tree)
      - HDCAM Tape 130, 2002-12-09, AFC 2019/001: MV130; afc2019001_0130; 47 min.; Wallace Hetaraka, Waipoua Forest, Tāne Mahuta (kauri tree)
      - HDCAM Tape 131, 2002-12-09, AFC 2019/001: MV131; afc2019001_0131; 44 min.; Wallace Hetaraka, Waipoua Forest, Tāne Mahuta (kauri tree)
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 111, 2002-12-07, AFC 2019/001: SR111; afc2019001_DAT0111; 1 hr. 30 min.; Wallace Hetaraka
      - DAT Tape 112, 2002-12-07, AFC 2019/001: SR112; afc2019001_DAT0112; 1 hr. 35 min.; Wallace Hetaraka
      - DAT Tape 113, 2002-12-07 to 2002-12-08, AFC 2019/001: SR113; afc2019001_DAT0113; 1 hr. 5 min.; Wallace Hetaraka, Terenga Paraoa (Maori marae [meeting house])
      - DAT Tape 114, 2002-12-09, AFC 2019/001: SR114; afc2019001_DAT0114; 1 hr. 34 min.; Wallace Hetaraka, Waipoua Forest, Tāne Mahuta (kauri tree)
  - Pawarenga, December 10-11, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 99 pages; English (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 8 pages; "Cemetary/Church," "Cutaways," "itv Malcolm at home," "MARAE" (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 132, 2002-12-10, AFC 2019/001: MV132; afc2019001_0132; 52 min.; Malcolm Peri
      - HDCAM Tape 133, 2002-12-10, AFC 2019/001: MV133; afc2019001_0133; 42 min.; Malcolm Peri
      - HDCAM Tape 134, 2002-12-10, AFC 2019/001: MV134; afc2019001_0134; 50 min.; Malcolm Peri
      - HDCAM Tape 135, 2002-12-10, AFC 2019/001: MV135; afc2019001_0135; 49 min.; Malcolm Peri
      - HDCAM Tape 136, 2002-12-10, AFC 2019/001: MV136; afc2019001_0136; 49 min.; Malcolm Peri
      - HDCAM Tape 137, 2002-12-11, AFC 2019/001: MV137; afc2019001_0137; 49 min.; Malcolm Peri, St. Gabriel's Church
      - HDCAM Tape 123, 2002-11-30 to 2002-12-11, AFC 2019/001: MV123; This item is also listed in Series 9, Bangalore.; afc2019001_0123; 49 min.; New computer blessing, Malcolm Peri, Maori marae (meeting house)
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 115, 2002-12-10, AFC 2019/001: SR115; afc2019001_DAT0115; 1 hr. 38 min.; Malcolm Peri
      - DAT Tape 116, 2002-12-10, AFC 2019/001: SR116; afc2019001_DAT0116; 1 hr. 34 min.; Malcolm Peri
      - DAT Tape 117, 2002-12-10 to 2002-12-11, AFC 2019/001: SR117; afc2019001_DAT0117; 1 hr. 24 min.; Malcolm Peri, St. Gabriel's Church
      - DAT Tape 118, 2002-12-11, AFC 2019/001: SR118; afc2019001_DAT0118; 27 min.; Malcolm Peri, Maori marae (meeting house)
- Series 11: Germany
  - Berlin, February 18-20, 2003
    - Manuscripts
      - Translations and transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 84 pages; German, English (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Translations and transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 141 pages; German, English (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Translations and transcriptions, 2003-04-15 to 2003-05-16, 11_Germany_Berlin_Translations and transcriptions; 6 files (.doc); German, English (Digital-content afc2019001_dc002)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-05-06 to 2003-10-14, 20 pages; "itv Jan Kelch," "itv Christoph Schmidt," "ITV Claudia A.," "itv Claudia B," "Itv Maria Reimelt," "archives," "itv Christoph Schmidt," "itv Claudia 2," "itv Claudia about Poussin," "itv Jan Kelch," "itv Maria +atelier Restauration," "Laboratoire," "Musée," "Radiography Rembrandt" (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 140, 2003-02-18, AFC 2019/001: MV140; afc2019001_0140; 49 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Maria Reimelt, Claudia Laurenze
      - HDCAM Tape 141, 2003-02-18, AFC 2019/001: MV141; afc2019001_0141; 49 min.; Gemäldegalerie, The man with the golden helmet ca. 1650-1660 by circle of Rembrandt
      - HDCAM Tape 142, 2003-02-18, AFC 2019/001: MV142; afc2019001_0142; 49 min.; Gemäldegalerie, The man with the golden helmet ca. 1650-1660 by circle of Rembrandt, David Rabinowitch
      - HDCAM Tape 143, 2003-02-19 to 2003-02-19, AFC 2019/001: MV143; afc2019001_0143; 53 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Hahn-Meitner-Institut Berlin
      - HDCAM Tape 144, 2003-02-19, AFC 2019/001: MV144; afc2019001_0144; 47 min.; Hahn-Meitner-Institut Berlin, Christoph Schmidt, Claudia Laurenze
      - HDCAM Tape 145, 2003-02-19 to 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: MV145; afc2019001_0145; 48 min.; Hahn-Meitner-Institut Berlin, Gemäldegalerie, Claudia Laurenze
      - HDCAM Tape 146, 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: MV146; afc2019001_0146; 48 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Claudia Laurenze
      - HDCAM Tape 147, 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: MV147; afc2019001_0147; 49 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Jan Kelch
      - HDCAM Tape 148, 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: MV148; afc2019001_0148; 49 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Jan Kelch, Christoph Schmidt
      - HDCAM Tape 149, 2002-03-01 to 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: MV149; afc2019001_0149; 28 min.; Screen test, Gemäldegalerie, Christoph Schmidt
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 140, 2003-02-18, AFC 2019/001: SR140; afc2019001_DAT0140; 1 hr. 35 min.; Gemäldegalerie
      - DAT Tape 141, 2003-02-18, AFC 2019/001: SR141; afc2019001_DAT0141; 48 min.; Gemäldegalerie
      - DAT Tape 142, 2003-02-19, AFC 2019/001: SR142; afc2019001_DAT0142; 1 hr. 39 min.; Hahn-Meitner-Institut Berlin
      - DAT Tape 143, 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: SR143; afc2019001_DAT0143; 1 hr. 26 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Claudia Laurenze
      - DAT Tape 144, 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: SR144; afc2019001_DAT0144; 1 hr. 22 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Jan Kelch
      - DAT Tape 145, 2003-02-20, AFC 2019/001: SR145; afc2019001_DAT0145; 35 min.; Gemäldegalerie, Christoph Schmidt
Appendix: Tape Inscriptions and Details
Attached is a searchable PDF list of the notes written on tape labels by the filmmakers. The information from their inscriptions about subject matter, location, and date have been incorporated throughout this finding aid, but are also listed verbatim in the Appendix for reference. The filmmakers' notes on recording specifications were not incorporated into the finding aid, but are listed in a separate column in the Appendix for reference.